<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220126</defName>
		<date>2022/01/26</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.3.0
- Fixed Conflict with Roads of the Rim.
- Added Tweak: Unlocked Meme Buildings - No memes required for buildable ideology stuff.
Added Tweak: Glowing Ambrosia - Makes Ambrosia glow so it's easier to spot.
Added Tweak: Glowing Healroot - Makes Healroot glow so it's easier to spot.
Added Tweak: Wild Reproduction - Wild animals can do the horizontal monster mash.
Added Tweak: Hunters Can Use Melee - Speaks for itself.
Added Tweak: Boomalopes Bleed Chemfuel - BURN BABAY!
Added Tweak: Disfigurement Penalty Multiplier - Ugly is the new Beautiful.
Added Tweak: Chatty Comms - Coms Console is a recreation source.
Added Tweak: Green Thumb - Restored Green Thumb trait.
Added Tweak: Herd Migration - Restored Herd Migration Event.
Added Tweak: Not So Wild Berries - Wild Berries now plantable.
Added Tweak: Room Size Tolerance - Better room size tolerances.
Added Tweak: Silent Doors - Disables the sound of doors opening and closing.
Added Tweak: Silent Mining - Disables the sound of mining.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220107</defName>
		<date>2022/01/07</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.2.0
- Added Tweak: Infestation Blocking Floors
- Added Tweak: No More Drop Pod Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Siege Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Sapper Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Breacher Raids</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220106</defName>
		<date>2022/01/06</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.1.0
- Added Tweak: Megasloth to Megatherium - Reverts the name change.
- Added Tweak: Impassable Deep Water - Prevents pawns navigating through deep water tiles.
- Added Tweak: Prisoners Don't Have Keys - Control whether or not prisoners and slaves can open doors.
- Added Tweak: Next Restock Timer - Shows when a settlement will next restock.

- Updated Tweak: Lag Free Lamps - Now includes darklight torches and braziers, as well as Vanilla Expanded candles and wall torches.
- Fixed Bug: Faster Smoothing - Now applies properly based on its setting.
- Fixed Bug: Power Usage Tweaks - Vanometric Power Cell now correctly provides instead of drains power.
- Fixed Conflict: Vanilla Ideology Expanded - Memes and Structure no longer blocks meme unlimiter.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

</Defs>