<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<!-- <O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220203</defName>
		<date>2022/02/03</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.5.0
Added: Wild Reproduction - Wild animals can do the horizontal monster mash.
Added: Green Thumb - Restored Green Thumb trait.
Added: Herd Migration - Restored Herd Migration Event.
Added: Silent Doors - Disables the sound of doors opening and closing.
Added: Silent Mining - Disables the sound of mining.
Added: Room Size Tolerance - Better room size tolerances.
Added: Disfigurement Penalty Multiplier - Ugly is the new Beautiful.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef> -->

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220620</defName>
		<date>2022/06/20</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.4.8206
- Added: Disable Desirable Apparel - Ideology option that disables those stupid fucking hats defaulting to showing up.
- Added: No Friend Shaped Manhunters - Allows control over parameters that can disable an animal from arriving on the map as a manhunter. 
- Added: Misanthrope Trait - Adds the Misanthrope trait (Dislikes People) and if a pawn was going to spawn with both Misandrist and Misogynist replaces them with Misanthrope.
- Added: Skill Rates Adjustment - Control skill gain or loss and a threshold to decide what level and above loss can happen at.
- Added: Trait Count Adjustment - Control how many traits pawns spawn with, within a min and max number.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220508</defName>
		<date>2022/05/08</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.4.8163
- Added: Boomalopes Bleed Chemfuel - BURN BABAY!
- Added: Chatty Comms - Coms Console is a recreation source.
- Added: Not So Wild Berries - Wild Berries now plantable.

- Fixed: Breakdowns no longer patches VFE - Power's reactor due to issues with it.
- Fixed: VIE - Memes and structures - It updated and broke the patch, now fixed.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220202</defName>
		<date>2022/02/02</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.3.0
- Fixed Conflict with Roads of the Rim.
- No Breakdowns is now disabled automatically if you use SOS2. It causes issues with SOS2.
- Added Tweak: Unlocked Meme Buildings - No memes required for buildable ideology stuff.
- Added Tweak: Slim Rim - Allows disabling of specific body types on human pawns.
- Added Tweak: Healroot to Xerigium - Switch the name of healroot back to its old one, Xerigium.
- Added Tweak: Darklight Glow Pods - Makes glowpods use darklight.
- Added Tweak: Glowing Ambrosia - Makes Ambrosia glow so it's easier to spot.
- Added Tweak: Glowing Healroot - Makes Healroot glow so it's easier to spot.
- Added Tweak: Hunters Can Use Melee - Speaks for itself.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220107</defName>
		<date>2022/01/07</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.2.0
- Added Tweak: Infestation Blocking Floors
- Added Tweak: No More Drop Pod Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Siege Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Sapper Raids
- Added Tweak: No More Breacher Raids</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

	<O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>
		<defName>O21_Tweaks_20220106</defName>
		<date>2022/01/06</date>
		<banner></banner>
		<content>Version 1.1.0
- Added Tweak: Megasloth to Megatherium - Reverts the name change.
- Added Tweak: Impassable Deep Water - Prevents pawns navigating through deep water tiles.
- Added Tweak: Prisoners Don't Have Keys - Control whether or not prisoners and slaves can open doors.
- Added Tweak: Next Restock Timer - Shows when a settlement will next restock.

- Updated Tweak: Lag Free Lamps - Now includes darklight torches and braziers, as well as Vanilla Expanded candles and wall torches.
- Fixed Bug: Faster Smoothing - Now applies properly based on its setting.
- Fixed Bug: Power Usage Tweaks - Vanometric Power Cell now correctly provides instead of drains power.
- Fixed Conflict: Vanilla Ideology Expanded - Memes and Structure no longer blocks meme unlimiter.</content>
		<linkUrl>https://outpost-21.fandom.com/wiki/Tweaks_Galore</linkUrl>
		<important>false</important>
	</O21Toolbox.UpdateListings.UpdateDef>

</Defs>